In this video, we'll put together everything we've learned in the previous videos to create
在这个视频中，我们将把之前学到的所有内容整合起来，创建一个端到端的客服助手的示例。
an end-to-end example of a customer service assistant.
我们将按照以下步骤进行。
We'll go through the following steps.
首先，我们将检查输入，看看它是否标记了审核API。
First, we'll check the input to see if it flags the moderation API.
其次，如果没有，我们将提取产品列表。
Second, if it doesn't, we'll extract the list of products.
第三，如果找到了产品，我们将尝试查找它们。
Third, if the products are found, we'll try to look them up.
第四，我们将使用模型回答用户问题。
And four, we'll answer the user question with the model.
最后，我们将通过审核API对答案进行审核。
And finally, we'll put the answer through the moderation API.
如果没有被标记，我们将把答案返回给用户。
And if it is not flagged, we'll return it to the user.
所以我们有了设置。
So we have our setup.
我们有这些额外的导入。
We have this additional imports.
这是一个用于聊天机器人UI的Python包。
This is a Python package we'll use for a chatbot UI.
所以我要粘贴一个处理用户消息的函数。
And so I'm going to paste in a function process user message.
然后我会先运行一个示例，然后我们会讨论这个函数。
And I'm actually going to run an example first, and then we'll talk through the function.
我们有我们一直在使用的用户输入。
So we have our user input that we've been using.
告诉我关于Smart X Pro手机和相机的信息。
Tell me about the Smart X Pro phone and the camera.
还要告诉我关于电视的信息。
Also tell me about TVs.
那么让我们运行它。
So let's run this.
首先，让我们运行它。
First, let's run this.
正如您所看到的，我们正在按照步骤回答用户的问题。
So as you can see, we're going through the steps to answer the user question.
因此，第一步是审核步骤，第二步是提取产品列表。
So the first step, the moderation step, the second step is extracting the list of products.
第三步是查找产品信息。
And so now with this product information, the model is trying to answer the question,
现在，有了这个产品信息，模型正在尝试回答问题，
as we've seen in the previous videos.
正如我们在之前的视频中所看到的。
And then finally, it puts the response through the moderation API again to make sure it's
最后，它再次通过审核API对响应进行审核，以确保它是
safe to show to the user.
安全向用户展示的。
And so this is the response that we're now familiar with.
这就是我们现在熟悉的响应。
And so let's talk through a little bit of what's happening.
让我们来谈谈正在发生的事情。
So we have our helper function process user message.
所以我们有一个帮助函数process user message。
Takes in the user input, which is the current message and an array of all of the messages
接收用户输入，即当前消息和所有消息的数组
so far.
到目前为止。
And this is when we build the chatbot UI.
这是我们构建聊天机器人UI的时候。
So the first step, checking to see if the input flags the moderation API.
第一步，检查输入是否标记了审核API。
We covered this in a previous video.
我们在之前的视频中介绍过这个。
If the input is flagged, then we tell the user that we can't process the request.
如果输入被标记，那么我们告诉用户我们无法处理请求。
If it is not flagged, we try to extract the list of products, as we did in the previous
如果没有被标记，我们尝试提取产品列表，就像在之前的
video.
视频中一样。
Then we try to look up the products.
然后我们尝试查找产品。
And in this case, if no products are found, this will just be an empty string.
在这种情况下，如果没有找到产品，这将只是一个空字符串。
Then we answer the user question.
然后我们回答用户的问题。
So we give the conversation history and the new messages with the relevant product information.
所以我们提供了与相关产品信息的对话历史记录和新消息。
So we get the response.
所以我们得到了响应。
And then we run this response through the moderation API.
然后我们将这个响应通过审核API运行。
If it's flagged, we tell the user that we can't provide this information.
如果被标记，我们告诉用户我们无法提供这些信息。
Maybe we'll say something, let me connect you.
也许我们会说些什么，让我为您连接。
And you could take some subsequent step.
然后您可以采取一些后续步骤。
And so let's put this all together with a nice UI and try to have a conversation.
因此，让我们将所有内容与漂亮的UI结合起来，尝试进行对话。
So here we have a function that will just accumulate the messages as we interact with
因此，这里有一个函数，它将随着我们与助手的交互而累积消息。
the assistant.
可以随意暂停视频，以更详细地了解其工作原理。
And feel free to pause the video to understand in more detail how this works.
当然，也可以对我们刚刚看到的非常长的处理用户消息函数进行相同的操作。
And of course, feel free to do the same for the really long process user message function
现在，我们将粘贴我们的代码以显示聊天机器人UI。
that we just saw as well.
如果我们运行这个，现在让我们尝试与客服助手进行对话。
So now we're going to paste in our code to display the chatbot UI.
所以让我们问一下，你们有哪些电视？
So if we run this, now let's try and have a conversation with the customer service assistant.
在幕后，助手正在执行处理用户消息函数中的所有步骤。
So let's ask, what TVs do you have?
所以让我们问一下，哪个是最便宜的？
And under the hood, the assistant is going through all of the steps in the process user
再次执行所有相同的步骤，但这次将对话历史记录传递到提示中。
message function.
好的，它告诉我们这个扬声器是我们拥有的最便宜的电视相关产品。
So it's listed a variety of different TVs.
有趣。
So now let's ask, which is the cheapest?
让我们看看最贵的是什么。
Again, it's going through all the same steps, but this time it's passing the conversation
所以最昂贵的电视是Cineview 8K电视。
history as well into the prompts.
所以让我们要求更多关于它的信息。
Okay, so it's telling us that this speaker is the cheapest TV related product we have.
告诉我更多关于它的信息。
Interesting.
有趣。
Let's see what the most expensive is.
让我们看看最贵的是什么。
So the most expensive TV is the Cineview 8K TV.
所以最昂贵的电视是Cineview 8K电视。
So let's ask for more information about it.
所以让我们要求更多关于它的信息。
Tell me more about it.
告诉我更多关于它的信息。
And so we've received some more information about this television.
因此，我们收到了有关这台电视的更多信息。
So in this example, we've combined the techniques we've learned throughout the course to create
在这个例子中，我们结合了课程中学到的技术，创建了一个综合系统，其中包含一系列步骤，评估用户输入，处理它们，
a comprehensive system with a chain of steps that evaluates user inputs, processes them,
然后检查输出。
and then checks the output.
通过监控系统在更多输入上的质量，您可以修改步骤，提高系统的整体性能。
By monitoring the quality of the system across a larger number of inputs, you can alter the
也许我们会发现，对于某些步骤，我们的提示可能更好，也许有些步骤甚至不必要。
steps and improve the overall performance of your system.
也许我们会找到更好的检索方法等等。
Maybe we might find that our prompts could be better for some of the steps, maybe some
我们将在下一个视频中进一步讨论这个问题。